<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MeetMap</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="newaccount">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="usu">User name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="pass">Password</string>
    <string name="repass">Repeat password</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="other">or sign up with</string>
    <string name="or">or </string>
    <string name="create">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="slide1">Welcome to MeetMap</string>
    <string name="slide2">Live new experiences with us</string>
    <string name="slide3">Connect with new people and create moments.</string>
    <string name="slide4">Experience together, remember together</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_app">MainAppActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="resetpass">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="fgPass">RESET PASSWORD</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="description">Your description</string>
    <string name="save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="telefono">Telephone number</string>
    <string name="surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="logout">LOG OUT</string>
    <string name="deleteaccount">Delete account</string>
    <string name="favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="favfragment">FAVOURITES FRAGMENT</string>
    <string name="chatfragment">CHAT FRAGMENT</string>
    <string name="exit">Log Out</string>
    <string name="editProfile">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="manusu">User manual</string>
    <string name="faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="createplan">New plan</string>
    <string name="question1">1. How does the app work?</string>
    <string name="answer1">The application has a main view of the location where you are and the closest plans, you can select any of them and a new window opens with all the information of that plan: name, place, date, price and a link to the web to be able to register</string>
    <string name="question2">2. How can I find activities and events near my location?</string>
    <string name="answer2">You must have the location of your mobile device activated and you will see some hand-shaped markers that indicate the places on the map where the plans are located</string>
    <string name="question3">3. How can I reserve a place in an event or activity?</string>
    <string name="answer3">When you find the plan you want, you can click on the map and it will take you to a window that provides you with all the information and a link to the website where you can reserve a place or sign up for the plan.</string>
    <string name="question4">4. Is there a reservation limit per event or activity?</string>
    <string name="answer4">The entity that makes them is in charge of managing the reservations and which can be accessed through the link of each plan that is offered from our application.</string>
    <string name="question5">5. How can I see the plans I like?</string>
    <string name="answer5">This app has the possibility of saving in favorites (click on the heart of each activity) the activities that you like the most and you can access that list in the favorites button in the lower menu of the application</string>
    <string name="question6">6. How can I unroll from a plan?</string>
    <string name="answer6">Each activity is managed by a different entity and it is that entity that should be contacted to consult the possibilities of canceling the plan or unsubscribing from the activity</string>
    <string name="question7">7. How can I make a suggestion or report a problem?</string>
    <string name="answer7">In the application there is a drop-down menu in the upper left part of the screen where an option to contact us is shown and you can write to us whenever you have a problem or a suggestion, we will attend to you as soon as possible trying to solve your problem or improve the app with your suggestions</string>
    <string name="question8">8. Does using the application have any cost?</string>
    <string name="answer8">The use of the application is free of charge. There is also no premium version or additional payments to have access to some extra functionality of the application. It is 100% free for all users</string>
    <string name="question9">9. Is the application available in my city/country?</string>
    <string name="answer9">Currently the application is only available for the city of Madrid, although in the not too distant future we plan to be present in more cities and countries. If you want it to be in your region, do not hesitate to contact us to send us your request!</string>
    <string name="question10">10. Can I contact the people who are signed up for the activity?</string>
    <string name="answer10">In the first versions of the app the chat is not yet available, as soon as possible you will have a chat available to contact all the people who are signed up for the activity and want to have conversations with the attendees of the activity or event</string>
    <string name="contactus">Contact us</string>
    <string name="suggestion">Suggestion or Incidence</string>
    <string name="send">SEND</string>
    <string name="textLarge" translatable="false">Lorem fistrum ese hombree hasta luego Lucas va usté muy cargadoo sexuarl de la pradera a wan ahorarr apetecan. La caidita la caidita te va a hasé pupitaa pecador ese pedazo de caballo blanco caballo negroorl quietooor. Jarl hasta luego Lucas papaar papaar tiene musho peligro se calle ustée te voy a borrar el cerito mamaar qué dise usteer.</string>
    <string name="large_text" translatable="false">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

</resources>