<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MeetMap</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="newaccount">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="usu">User name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="pass">Password</string>
    <string name="repass">Repeat password</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="other">or sign up with</string>
    <string name="other2">or log in with</string>
    <string name="or">or </string>
    <string name="create">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="slide1">Welcome to MeetMap</string>
    <string name="slide2">Live new experiences with us</string>
    <string name="slide3">Connect with new people and create moments.</string>
    <string name="slide4">Experience together, remember together</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_app">MainAppActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="resetpass">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="fgPass">RESET PASSWORD</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="description">Your description</string>
    <string name="save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="telefono">Telephone number</string>
    <string name="surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="logout">LOG OUT</string>
    <string name="deleteaccount">Delete account</string>
    <string name="favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="favfragment">FAVOURITES FRAGMENT</string>
    <string name="chatfragment">CHAT FRAGMENT</string>
    <string name="exit">Log Out</string>
    <string name="editProfile">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="manusu">User manual</string>
    <string name="faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="createplan">New plan</string>
    <string name="question1">1. How does the app work?</string>
    <string name="answer1">The application has a main view of the location where you are and the closest plans, you can select any of them and a new window opens with all the information of that plan: name, place, date, price and a link to the web to be able to register</string>
    <string name="question2">2. How can I find activities and events near my location?</string>
    <string name="answer2">You must have the location of your mobile device activated and you will see some hand-shaped markers that indicate the places on the map where the plans are located</string>
    <string name="question3">3. How can I reserve a place in an event or activity?</string>
    <string name="answer3">When you find the plan you want, you can click on the map and it will take you to a window that provides you with all the information and a link to the website where you can reserve a place or sign up for the plan.</string>
    <string name="question4">4. Is there a reservation limit per event or activity?</string>
    <string name="answer4">The entity that makes them is in charge of managing the reservations and which can be accessed through the link of each plan that is offered from our application.</string>
    <string name="question5">5. How can I see the plans I like?</string>
    <string name="answer5">This app has the possibility of saving in favorites (click on the heart of each activity) the activities that you like the most and you can access that list in the favorites button in the lower menu of the application</string>
    <string name="question6">6. How can I unroll from a plan?</string>
    <string name="answer6">Each activity is managed by a different entity and it is that entity that should be contacted to consult the possibilities of canceling the plan or unsubscribing from the activity</string>
    <string name="question7">7. How can I make a suggestion or report a problem?</string>
    <string name="answer7">In the application there is a drop-down menu in the upper left part of the screen where an option to contact us is shown and you can write to us whenever you have a problem or a suggestion, we will attend to you as soon as possible trying to solve your problem or improve the app with your suggestions</string>
    <string name="question8">8. Does using the application have any cost?</string>
    <string name="answer8">The use of the application is free of charge. There is also no premium version or additional payments to have access to some extra functionality of the application. It is 100% free for all users</string>
    <string name="question9">9. Is the application available in my city/country?</string>
    <string name="answer9">Currently the application is only available for the city of Madrid, although in the not too distant future we plan to be present in more cities and countries. If you want it to be in your region, do not hesitate to contact us to send us your request!</string>
    <string name="question10">10. Can I contact the people who are signed up for the activity?</string>
    <string name="answer10">In the first versions of the app the chat is not yet available, as soon as possible you will have a chat available to contact all the people who are signed up for the activity and want to have conversations with the attendees of the activity or event</string>
    <string name="contactus">Contact us</string>
    <string name="suggestion">Suggestion or Incidence</string>
    <string name="send">SEND</string>
    <string name="infocontactus">We will respond as soon as possible, check the email you provide in this form</string>
    <string name="textLarge" translatable="false">Lorem fistrum ese hombree hasta luego Lucas va usté muy cargadoo sexuarl de la pradera a wan ahorarr apetecan. La caidita la caidita te va a hasé pupitaa pecador ese pedazo de caballo blanco caballo negroorl quietooor. Jarl hasta luego Lucas papaar papaar tiene musho peligro se calle ustée te voy a borrar el cerito mamaar qué dise usteer.</string>
    <string name="updatedData"> Updated data</string>
    <string name="emailRequired">Email is required</string>
    <string name="passRequired">Password is required</string>
    <string name="repassRequired">Repeat password is required</string>
    <string name="emailValid">Email is not valid</string>
    <string name="passNeeds">Password needs: Capital letters, small letters, numbers and must be longer than 6 characters</string>
    <string name="passSame">Passwords must be the same</string>
    <string name="verifyEmail">Please verify your email</string>
    <string name="emailExists">This email alredy exists</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="autenticationError">User authentication failed</string>
    <string name="incorrectEmailPass">Incorrect email or password</string>
    <string name="accountNotExists">The account does not exists. Please register</string>
    <string name="checkMail">Check your email to reset your password</string>
    <string name="tryAgain">Try again, something wrong happened</string>
    <string name="date">Date: </string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule: </string>
    <string name="place">Place: </string>
    <string name="link">+Info</string>
    <string name="formSubmit">Form submitted successfully</string>
    <string name="noHayInfo">The company of the activity does not offer more information, go to the center or the web to find it</string>
    <string name="dateInfo">No date set</string>
    <string name="hourInfo">No set time</string>
    <string name="placeInfo">No place set</string>
    <string name="location">Go to settings and accept the location permision</string>
    <string name="backAgain">Please click BACK again to exit</string>
    <string name="deleteAccountQuestion">Are you sure you want to delete the account?</string>
    <string name="deleteAccountSuccesful">The account has been deleted</string>
    <string name="messagechat">Message</string>
    <string name="nochats">"It's too quiet around here..."</string>

</resources>